Sigh. Hello!
We are...I mean...I am Peazzo, a Sister
in Training of the Church. How do?
and this timid little thing
is my fellow sister in
training i'm lino we heard
there were intruders from
the dark territory lurking
about are you they huh i
think i'll let you handle
this one they look annoying
um we are sort of we're
actually from the human
realm not the dark territory
As for intruding here,
I guess we are. Technically.
Well, Nell, do these two look
anything like monsters to you? Huh?
Where are their horns and tails?
But how should I know?
I was just telling you what
the books said they look like.
You're the one jumping
to conclusions, Seal.
Ladies? We'll go.
If someone sees us, you'll get in trouble.
Don't worry, there's no
chance of that happening.
This morning, the church
ordered all the monks,
nuns, and apprentices to stay in
their quarters and lock their doors.
This was the perfect
opportunity for us to sneak
out and have a look at
these nasty intruders.
They're human.
Yes, very.
We heard you were arrested, but broke
your spiritual chains and escaped.
We also heard you defeated
two Integrity Knights!
That's why I was sure you were
monsters from the Dark Territory.
Either that or Knights of Darkness.
I'm sure you can understand why
we were so curious about you.
One last thing?
Do you mind telling us
what your names are?
Not at all. I'm Eugeo.
And this here is Kirito.
Do you not have last names?
No.
My family are settlers.
And do you have last names? Yes.
We've been waiting to share them with you.
My full name, Sinner, is Lino Synthesis
F
F G
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
I don't know what pain
is, but it doesn't matter.
I've opened my eyes and opened my eyes.
I'm going to connect with you.
I'm going to run away.
I'll be back to the end of my life.
I'll be back to the end
of
my
life.
Yu-Gi-Oh! Yu-Gi-Oh!
My name is Beezel Synthesis 29.
You're...
...tec -
Don't fret, Eugeo, without a last name.
You're ours now.
It's a paralysis poison.
We don't want you to die yet.
Not until we get you to
the 50th floor anyway.
I'm sure you must be wondering.
How in the world did these two little
girls become Integrity Knights?
We were born and raised
inside the Central Cathedral.
One day, Administrator herself ordered
the monks and nuns here to create us.
She needed test subjects
for a sacred arch she was
experimenting with that
could resurrect the dead.
We received our callings when we were
five, earlier than other children.
Our job was to kill each other.
We were given little swords
that looked like toys.
Then we'd peer off and take
turns stabbing each other.
At first, administrators' attempts at
resurrection were, how shall I say,
not so good.
There were some children who exploded.
And others who ended up
as weird blobs of flesh?
And still others who returned but were...
different
We were being resurrected over and over.
But we didn't like dying in pain.
So the two of us researched
how to kill with one strike.
We found that if we killed
cleanly, it didn't hurt as much.
And the odds of being successfully
resurrected were higher.
But the problem was deciding
which strike worked the best.
We narrowed it down to lopping off
the head or a quick stab to the heart.
They both worked equally well.
In the end, though,
Administrator decided it was too difficult
to master the Sacred Art of Resurrection.
We were about eight years old
when she abandoned the experiment.
When it started, there were thirty of us.
But Seal and i were the only survivors.
Then, administrator made a special
exception and made us integrity knights.
Well, to a certain degree.
She said we hadn't learned enough to go
on guard duty like the other knights.
So we've been studying
the laws and sacred arts
with the other apprentices
for the past two years.
To be honest, we're tired of it.
Earlier today,
we were discussing ways to earn our
dragons and divine objects more quickly.
We heard that minions from the Dark
Territory had infiltrated the Cathedral.
So we thought, if we could capture and
execute them before the other knights could,
it would show Administrator how capable we
were and she would make
us full-bledged knights.
So, we waited on the stairs.
We're truly sorry for using poison on you.
It was our only option.
You see, we wanted to bring you to
the 50th floor alive if possible.
Oh, and when we do get
there, don't you worry.
Fiesel and I are really good at killing.
It won't hurt at all.
Well, well, if it isn't all
four of the Whirling Blades.
As well as Vice Commander
Fanatio Synthesis, too.
The whole Senate must be in a panic.
Why else would they ask you here,
Fanatio of the Heaven-Piercing Blade?
You apprentices should not be on the
battlefield with honorable knights.
Now that is funny.
It's because you bring honor
and tradition into battle
that you so-called mighty
integrity knights lost.
Not once but twice!
But don't you worry?
As you can see,
we caught the intruders
and we'll make sure the
reputation of the knights
won't be sullied any further!
You can count on that!
She's right!
We're going to decapitate these
sinners right here and now!
So watch closely and make sure to give
an accurate report to the Pontifex!
You are honorable knights, after all!
We trust you not to steal our...
For credit, that would be cowardly.
No fair...
I can't...
It'll wear off in a minute
as soon as you can move
your lips again recite
your perfect weapon art.
But keep it down this ain't
gonna work if the night's here.
When it's ready to go hang on
to it a bit wait for my signal.
I'm sure you're wondering
how in the world can i move.
You gave yourselves away
you said all the monks
nuns and apprentices were
ordered to stay in their.
Rooms and if you're a
monk nun or apprentice
there's no way you'd
disobey the church's order.
But you weren't in your
rooms you were looking
for us so that meant
you guys weren't real.
Apprentices i also noticed
those scabbards you
got are made of ruby oak
they use that wood to.
hold swords made of
toxic rubaril steel. Why?
Because it's the only thing that
won't rot against the blade.
There's no way you'd have
something like that if you
were sisters in training.
That's why I started reciting
a poison-neutralizing
art before you got near us.
It took a while to kick
in, but what can you do?
There's more to strength
than being fast with a sword.
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
I'm going to teach you a lesson today.
You're going to watch
these knights you made fun
of fight and see what
real strength's all about.
Sorry for the wait,
Vice Commander Fanatio.
My name's Kirito, the Swordsman!
How dare you do battle
with a vice commander?
The Four Whirling Blades
are your opponents here.
Turn and face us.
Hold your position.
This one is mine.
As you wish.
System call.
Enhance armament!
No!
My voice, it's back.
System call.
Criminal or no, if you lived in Senator,
you should know what a mirror is.
It is an instrument capable of
reflecting Solas's light completely.
Long ago, the Pontifex gathered
1,000 enormous mirrors.
To focus Solas's midsummer light,
creating a pure white flame.
It was so hot, it melted a
human-sized boulder within minutes.
The Pontifex, using her holy skills.
Fused the 1,000 mirrors together, then
honed them to create a magnificent sword.
This sword, the heaven-piercing blade.
Know this,
your stomach and foot were punctured by
the glorious power of the sun god Solus.
It reflects the sun's energy.
Now, sinner, prepare to meet your end.
Destroyed!
Don't you dare look at me.
Your eyes are laced with disdain.
Just like his.
You men think my gender affects
the quality of my skill?
Even sinners deny me respect!
I command you to fight me in earnest.
I am a knight.
An integrity knight.
I get it.
Your sword and skill, it's a cover.
It let you stand back and fire shots
and hide the fact you're a woman.
Ain't that right, Lady Fanatio?
How dare you!
Just so you know,
the reason I looked so shocked before,
it wasn't because you're a woman.
It's because when you lost your
helmet, you lost all your nerve.
I know why you hide your
face under that helmet.
If anyone here's got a problem
with you being a woman, it's you.
Silence!
You wretch!
I shall kill you!
You want to try? Go ahead.
I know what it's like to fight and
lose to women, and you know what?
I never held back for
them, and I won't for you!
No way! No way!
I was wrong.
You are different.
Although you may be a sinner,
you are quite unlike the other
men I have fought before.
None of them had your spirit.
Their attacks all lacked conviction
once they saw my detestable face.
Detestable? Okay.
Then, how come you comb your hair and
put on lipstick if you wear a helmet?
You don't do it for
yourself, that's for sure.
You're bitter because you can't have
the person you love, and you know why?
It's because the Church and
the Pontifect say you can't.
Well, I'm here to destroy them and
free everyone from their tyranny!
I can tell you are no agent of
darkness, as the Prime Minister claimed.
Regardless, you are still
extremely dangerous.
You would disrupt the Church and the
Knighthood, not just with your sword,
but with your words.
You also put the human empire
in peril, and that, sir,
is a knight's duty to protect.
You speak the truth,
but I am obliged to defeat you, even
if it sullies my pride as a knight.
Hidden light of the heaven-piercing
blade, cast off your shackles.
Release recollection!
You idiot.
You're gonna kill us all!
Now's my chance.
My only chance!
Enhanced Sparbonnet!
Blue Rose Bloom!
Damn that rat!
Kirito, are you hurt?
Don't move, I'll heal you.
I'm fine.
Don't let up, keep at it!
She's tough.
This ain't enough to stop her?
System call!
You knights, you're all the same!
You're all heartless!
Stop fighting!
Stop or die!
It's no use.
I can't win.
I can't beat her.
You're letting hate get the
better of you, Yu-Gi-Oh.
Stop it.
You didn't come this far because you
hated the Integrity Knights, did you?
You're here to get Alice back.
You're here because you love her.
But guess what?
That Integrity Knight, she feels
just as strong about her duty.
And I'm no different.
I want to protect everyone in this world.
You.
Alice.
Even this night, we're so close,
and we can't afford to give up now.
Ain't that right, Yu-Gi-Oh?
Enhance Armament!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
And everything turns to dust to dust
Next time, the Osmanthus Knight.